wigetmedia.com 2019-10-11

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy
Wiget Group AB (referred to as “Wiget Group AB” or “we” or “us” or “our”) is committed to
protecting and respecting your privacy and handling your personal data in an open and
transparent manner. The personal data that we collect and process may vary depending on the
service we provide to you.
This privacy policy:
          ●   Provides an overview of how Wiget Group collects and processes your personal
              data, and informs you about your rights under the EU General Data Protection
              Regulation (“GDPR”) and any national law supplementing or implementing the
              GDPR,
          ● contains important information about, among others, the collection and use of
              personal data; the legal grounds for the processing of that data; disclosures of that
              personal data to third parties and the use of cookies on the Website.
For the purposes of this privacy policy:
          ●   when we refer to “personal data” we mean data which identifies or may identify you
              and which may include, for example, your name, address, identification number,
              telephone number, date of birth and occupation,
          ●   when we refer to “processing” we mean the handling of your personal data by us,
              including collecting, protecting and storing your personal data, and
          ●   when we refer to our “Website” or our “Platform” we mean www.wigetmedia.com.
Who we are
Wiget Group AB is a company registered in Sweden, under registration number 556842-1167 as
a limited liability company having its registered office at Kocksgatan 1, 116 24 Stockholm,
Sweden.
Our Data Protection Principles

We adhere to the principles relating to processing of personal data set out in the GDPR which
require personal data to be:
         1. Processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner (Lawfulness, Fairness and
             Transparency).
         2. Collected only for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes (Purpose Limitation).
         3. Adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary in relation to the purposes for
             which it is Processed (Data Minimisation).
         4. Accurate and where necessary kept up to date (Accuracy).
         5. Not kept in a form which permits identification of data subjects for longer than is
             necessary for the purposes for which the data is Processed (Storage Limitation).
         6. Processed in a manner that ensures its security using appropriate technical and
             organisational measures to protect against unauthorised or unlawful processing and
             against accidental loss, destruction or damage (Security, Integrity and
             Confidentiality).
         7. Not transferred to another country without appropriate safeguards being in place
             (Transfer Limitation).
         8. Made available to data subjects and data subjects allowed to exercise certain rights
             in relation to their Personal Data (Data Subject’s Rights and Requests).
         9. We are responsible for and must be able to demonstrate compliance with the data
             protection principles listed above (Accountability).
Privacy Policy
Date May 25, 2018
1. Data Controller
1.1 This privacy policy applies where we are acting as a data controller with respect to your
personal data and therefore determine the purposes and means of the processing of that
personal data.
1.3 We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy
when you first visit our Website.
1.4 Our Website incorporates privacy controls you can use to specify whether you would like to
receive marketing, limit the publication or any other use of your information. You can access
such privacy controls via hello@wigetmedia.com.
2. How we collect your personal data

2.1 We obtain your personal data mainly through any information you provide directly to us or
through information provided by third parties. Below is a list of ways in which we collect your
personal data.
Personal data collected directly from you, including:
          ●   when you in your own name or on behalf of a legal entity (our Customer) complete
              our Publisher or Advertiser ( both referred to as our “Customer”) registration forms,
              which are available on our Website,
          ● when you enter and use our Website, and/or performing contractual obligations,
              and
          ● when you contact us for any enquiries, complaints or for any other reason.
Personal data collected from other sources, including:
          ●   via third parties including our business partners, contractors and/or vendors in a
              manner that is permitted,
          ● through tags in websites you use and/or manage or control.
3. Personal Data We Use, Purposes and Legal Grounds
We may collect the following personal data from you depending on the service we provide to you.
We will only process your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use
your personal data in the following circumstances:
Type of information               Purpose                          Legal basis of processing

Data about your use of our To analyse the operation of our Legitimate                   interests   in
Website.                          Website and services.                monitoring and improving our
                                                                       Website and services.
IP       address,    geographical
location, browser type and
version,     operating    system,
referral source, length of visit,
page views, website navigation
paths, timing, frequency, pattern
of your service use.
Profile data.                     Operating our Website, providing Legitimate interests in the proper
                                  our services, communicating with administration of our Website.
Your name, address, telephone you. Fulfilment of KYC/AML
number, email address, gender, procedures.                             Performing the contract we have
date of birth.                                                         with you or Customer.
Publication data.                 The publication data may be Legitimate interests for the
                                  processed for the purposes of proper administration of our
Information that you post for enabling such publication and Website and business.
publication on our Website or administering our Website and
through our services.             services.                            Performing the contract we have
                                                                       with you or Customer.
Inquiry data.                     The inquiry data may be processed Performing the contract we have
                                  for the purposes of fulfilment of with you or Customer.
                                  our KYC and AML obligations.
                                  The proper performance of our Legitimate interests
                                  payment obligations to you or
                                  Customer.
Transaction data.                 The transaction data may be Performing the contract we have
                                  processed for the purpose of with you or Customer.
The transaction data, your payments and keeping proper Legitimate interests
contact details, your/Customer records of those transactions.
card details and the transaction
details.
Notification data.                The notification data may be Performing the contract we have
                                  processed for the purposes of with you.
                                  sending      you     the    relevant Legitimate interests
                                  notifications and/or newsletters.

Correspondence data.              The proper performance of our Performing the contract we have
                                  contractual obligation to you or with you or Customer.
The communication content and Customer.
metadata associated with the                                           Legitimate interests
communication.
Any of your personal data Exercise or defence of legal Our legitimate interests.
identified in this policy.        claims,      whether      in   court
                                  proceedings or in an administrative
                                  or out-of-court procedure, the
                                  protection and assertion of our
                                  legal rights, your legal rights and
                                  the legal rights of others.
Any of your personal data The obtaining or maintaining Our legitimate interests.
identified in this policy         insurance coverage, managing
                                  risks, or obtaining professional
                                  advice.
4. Information We May Provide to Third Parties
We may disclose your personal data to the third parties listed below. When we do so, we require
those third parties to have appropriate technical and organisational measures in place to protect
your personal data. We will not share any of your personal data for any purpose other than the
purposes described in this privacy policy, nor will we sell your personal data to anyone.
4.1 Any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding
company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and on the
legal bases, set out in this privacy policy.
4.2 To our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the
purposes of managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or
defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court
procedure.
4.3 Payment services providers we have chosen to support us with financial transactions relating
to our Website. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the
extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and
dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.
4.4 Governmental and regulatory bodies, including law enforcement authorities, in connection
with enquiries, proceedings or investigations by such parties or in order to enable Propeller to
comply with its legal and regulatory requirements.

4.5 Partners, contractors and/or vendors in order to perform contract we have with you or
Customer.
5. Your data protection rights
You have the following rights in terms of the personal data we hold about you:
The right to be informed.      Wiget Group AB is publishing this privacy policy to keep you informed
                               as to what we do with your personal data. You can ask us for information
                               regarding any data of yours that we keep at any time. This information
                               concerns, among other things, the data categories we process, for what
                               purposes we process them, the origin of the data if we did not acquire
                               them directly from you and, if applicable, the recipients to whom we have
                               sent your data.
The right to access.           This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you
                               and to check that we are lawfully processing it. You can obtain a copy of
                               your data from us free of charge. If you are interested in other copies, we
                               reserve the right to charge for the additional copies.
The right to        correction You can request that we correct your data. We will initiate appropriate
(rectification).               measures to keep the data of yours that we continuously process correct,
                               complete, and up to date, based the latest information available to us.
The right to erasure           You can request that we delete your data provided the legal requirements
                               have been met. In accordance with Article 17 the GDPR, this can be the
(The right to be forgotten). case if:
                                          ●    the data are no longer required for the purposes they were
                                               acquire or otherwise processed;
                                          ● you revoke your consent, which is the basis of the data
                                               processing, and there is no other legal basis for the
                                               processing;
                                          ● you object to the processing of your data and there are no
                                               legitimate reasons for the processing or you object to data
                                               processing for the purposes of direct advertising;
                                          ● the data have been processed illegally.
                               We may however still process data:
                                          ●    To ensure adherence to a legal obligation that requires us to
                                               process your data
                                          ●    In particular with regard to legal retention periods
                                          ●    To assert, exercise or defend against legal claims

The     right    to    restrict You can request that we restrict the processing of your data if
processing.
                                            ●  You dispute the correctness of the data – for the period of
                                               time we need to check the correctness of the data;
                                            ●  The processing is illegal but you do not wish to have your
                                               data deleted and request a restriction of use instead;
                                            ●  We no longer need your data, but you need them to assert,
                                               exercise or defend against legal claims;
                                            ●  You have filed an objection to the processing, though it has
                                               not yet been decided whether our legitimate grounds
                                               outweigh yours.
The right to data portability. At your request, we will transfer your data– where technically possible –
                                to another responsible entity.
                                However, this right only applies if the data processing is based on your
                                consent or is required to fulfill a contract. Instead of receiving a copy of
                                your data, you can ask us to send the data directly to another responsible
                                entity that you specify.
The right to object.            You can object to the processing of your data at any time for reasons that
                                arise from your special situation provided the data processing is based on
                                your consent or our legitimate interest or that of a third party. In this case,
                                we will no longer process your data. The latter does not apply if we are
                                able to prove there are compelling, defensible reasons for the processing
                                that outweigh your interests or we require your data to assert, exercise or
                                defend against legal claims.
The right      to    withdraw Withdraw the consent you gave us with regard to the processing of your
consent.                        personal data for certain purposes, such as to allow us to promote our
                                products and services to you.
The right to complain.          Wiget Group AB takes your rights very seriously. However, if you are of
                                the opinion that we have not dealt with your complaints adequately, you
                                have the right to submit a complaint to the data privacy protection
                                authorities responsible. You can visit their website to find out how to
                                submit a complaint (https://www.datainspektionen.se/).
We endeavour to address all of your requests promptly.
6. International Transfers of Your Personal Data
6.1 We do not envisage that any of your personal data will be transferred to countries outside the
European Economic Area (EEA) as our offices, facilities, subcontractors and other third parties
with which we work are all located within the EEA.

6.2 In the event that this changes in the future and one or more recipients of your personal data
are located outside the EEA, where data protection laws may be of a lower standard than in the
EEA, we will impose the same data protection safeguards that we deploy inside the EEA to
ensure that your personal data are always protected.
7. Retaining and Deleting Personal Data
7.1 We will keep your personal data for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which we
initially collected them. Once such period has ended, we will keep your personal data for the
longest of the following periods: a) any retention period set out in our retention policy which is in
line with regulatory requirements relating to retention; or (b) the end of the period in which legal
action or investigations might arise in respect of the services provided.
7.2 Once the retention period of your personal data lapses, we will ensure that your personal
data are either irreversibly anonymised or securely destroyed.
8. Confidentiality and Security
8.1 We deploy various security measures such as encryption and authentication tools in line with
the current state of the art to protect and maintain the security, integrity and availability of your
personal data.
8.2 100% protection against unauthorised access in the case of data transfers across the internet
or a website cannot be guaranteed, but we and our service providers and business partners do
our utmost to protect your personal data in line with the prevailing data protection legislation by
means of physical and electronic physical precautions. Among other things, we use the following
measures:
           ●    Strict criteria for authorisation to access your personal data on a “need-to-know”
                basis only and exclusively for the specified purpose;
           ● Transfer of acquired data in secured form;
           ● Storage of confidential data in our secure servers;
           ● Firewall safeguarding of IT systems to provide protection against unauthorised
                access, and
           ● Continuous monitoring of access to IT systems to detect and prevent the misuse of
                personal data.
8.3 If you have received a password from us in order to be able to access certain parts of our
Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and for compliance with all
other security procedures which we make you aware from time to time. We ask you not to share
your password with anyone.
9. Cookies

9.1. Our Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Website and provide
contractual obligations in a high quality level. This helps us to ensure its smooth operation in
order to improve your experience.
10. Changes to this privacy policy
10.1 We may update this privacy policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our
Website.
10.2 We will notify you appropriately when we make changes to the privacy policy and we will
amend its revision date so that you know when we last amended it. We do however encourage
you to review this statement periodically so as to always be informed about how we are
processing and protecting your personal information.
10.3 We may notify you of changes to this policy by email or through our Website.
11 Contacts
11.1. If you have any questions about our privacy policy or wish to obtain more details in relation
to the personal data we process about you or wish to exercise any of your rights set out in
Section 5, please contact us via email at: hello@wigetmedia.com
